The Final Chapter
Puppet Master 5 is a horror, fantasy, science
fiction film directed by Jeff Burr.
Sutekh, the dark pharaoh from another dimension, sends his own puppet, Totem, to continue
his quest to kill Rick and steal the magic which animates the puppets.
Rick Myers, played by Gordon Currie.
Susie, played by Chandra West.
Dr. Jennings, played by Ian Ogilvy.
Lauren, played by Teresa Hill.
Andre Toulon, played by Guy Rolfe.
Hendy, played by Nicholas Guest.
Puppet Master (also titled The Puppet Master and Puppetmaster) is a 1989
American horror film written by Charles Band and Kenneth J.
Hall, and directed by David Schmoeller.
The film stars Paul Le Mat, Irene Miracle, Matt Roe and Kathryn O'Reilly as psychics who are
plotted against by a former colleague, using puppets animated by an Egyptian spell.
Originally intended for summer 1989 theatrical release, before being released on home video the following September, Puppet Master was ultimately pushed to
a direct-to-video release on October 12, 1989, as Band felt this was likely to be more financially successful than the theatrical market.
It was very popular and has since developed a large cult
following, and an extensive franchise.
The film explores themes of hotel, puppet, sequel, evil doll, demon.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.